말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
Hey, what you doin’?
기다리잖아 Call back, uh
온도 Check 했잖아 나 꽁했어
추워 나 감기고 싶어
Hurry up 이불 가져와 덮어줘
I wanna touch you
But you’re in the laptop
날 보러 와
커피처럼 Take out
딩디기딩 Like a 리기딩딩
너랑 같이 빙빙 놀고 싶어 Errtime
내 맘이 간질간질해 I’m sick
Always you and me like a symphony
We come together
너의 넘치는 매력
You make a bad day better yeah you
You make a good day better too
눈을 뜨는 아침부터
달이 지는 새벽까지
네 생각에 행복해
아마 모를걸
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
L.O.V.E, L.O.V.E
흐트러진 퍼즐같이
입안에 담고 있는 말
이제는 말하고 싶어
Tonight 이제 그만 고민하고
Yeah boy, I’d like 날 거부하지 마 so
눈을 뜨는 아침부터
달이 지는 새벽까지
네 생각에 행복해
아마 모를걸
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
오 널 처음 본 순간부터
자꾸 내 꿈에 나와
눈 뜨면 아쉬워
No need to rush
좀 더 다가갈게 난 Little
I’m waiting on you too
Every day gets better
So glad that I found you
말하고 싶어
To say I love you
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
And in this moonlight
We’re reaching new highs
But boy, I like you
Really really like you
Okay okay 내가 졌으니까
오늘 너의 맘을 허락해
Okay okay 별이 떴으니까
손잡고 눈을 감을게
Okay okay 말을 섞으니까
말풍선이 가득해
But boy, I like you
Really really like you